Guide to the R. Stuart Hummel Family Papers M1607
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series I. STUART FAMILY PAPERS, 1874-1940
  - Subseries I. RACHEL ANNA GOLDEN STUART, 1880-1940
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to Mildred Stuart Hummel, January-March, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Letter 11 (Box 5, Folder 5, Item Letter 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 14)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to Mildred Stuart Hummel, April-June, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Letter 1 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 17)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to Mildred Stuart Hummel, July-September, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Letter 1 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 14)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to Mildred Stuart Hummel, October-December, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Letter 1 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 20)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to Mildred Stuart Hummel, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to Mildred Stuart Hummel, 1932-1934 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to William F. Hummel, circa 1910-1927 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to R. Stuart Hummel family, 1926-1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to nieces and nephews, miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart to nieces and nephews, 1885-1933 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 12)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart and Board of Missions, correspondence, 1912-1946 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Abram and Rachel Jane Golden to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1893-1910 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 28)
      - Letter 29 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 29)
      - Letter 30 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 30)
      - Letter 31 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 31)
      - Letter 32 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 32)
      - Letter 33 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 33)
      - Letter 34 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 34)
      - Letter 35 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 35)
      - Letter 36 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 36)
      - Letter 37 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 37)
    - Alcy Jane Golden to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1894-1928 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 15)
    - Alice Golden to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1894-1914 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 14)
    - Emily Golden to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1893-1921 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 19)
    - William Melvin Golden to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1910-1912 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 3)
    - June and Isabelle Hummel to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1922-1926 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 8)
    - Nieces and nephews to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1894-1933 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 6, Folder 14, Item 15)
    - Relatives to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Relatives to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1895-1924 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Letter 1 (Box 6, Folder 16, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 6, Folder 16, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 6, Folder 16, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 6, Folder 16, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 6, Folder 16, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 6, Folder 16, Item 6)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1880-1899 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Letter 1 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 28)
      - Letter 29 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 29)
      - Letter 30 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 30)
      - Letter 31 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 31)
      - Letter 32 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 32)
      - Letter 33 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 33)
      - Letter 34 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 34)
      - Letter 35 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 35)
      - Letter 36 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 36)
      - Letter 37 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 37)
      - Letter 38 (Box 7, Folder 2, Item 38)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1900-1904 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Letter 1 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 28)
      - Letter 29 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 29)
      - Letter 30 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 30)
      - Letter 31 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 31)
      - Letter 32 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 32)
      - Letter 33 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 33)
      - Letter 34 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 34)
      - Letter 35 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 35)
      - Letter 36 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 36)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1905-1908 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Letter 1 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 28)
      - Letter 29 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 29)
      - Letter 30 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 30)
      - Letter 31 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 31)
      - Letter 32 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 32)
      - Letter 33 (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 33)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1909-1911 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Letter 1 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 15)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Letter 1 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 18)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1912-1913 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Letter 1 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 28)
      - Letter 29 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 29)
      - Letter 30 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 30)
      - Letter 31 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 31)
      - Letter 32 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 32)
      - Letter 33 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 33)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Letter 1 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 28)
      - Letter 29 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 29)
      - Letter 30 (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 30)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Letter 1 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 11)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Letter 1 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1917-1923 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Letter 1 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 20)
    - Friends to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Letter 1 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 16)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, incoming memo, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, miscellaneous documents, 1895-1918 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, miscellaneous documents, circa 1920- (Box 8, Folder 6)